www.bogjerlow.com



bgjerlow@live.com +45 27 29 69 15 Pittevej 9, 8881 Thorsø, Denmark

Skills

User Interface Design
Web Development
User Experience Design
Web Content / Copywriting

Profile

Multimedia Designer from Denmark specialising in user interface design and front-end development. I am passionate about creating beautiful user interfaces with a focus on the user experience. Currently living in Denmark, but am prepared to relocate elsewhere within Europe.

Tools

Software

Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe InDesign

Sketch InVision

Front-end

HTML
CSS
Sass
JavaScript

jQuery

Back-end

Ruby on Rails

SQL

Other

Git/GitHub WordPress

Languages

Danish (Native)
English (Fluent)
German (Elementary)

Education

Multimedia Design and Communication @ Business Academy Aarhus

2015 - 2017

Work Experience

Freelancer @ Gjerlow Solutions

February 2018 - Present

• Freelance UI/UX design and web development

Multimedia Designer @ Carswip

November 2017 - January 2018

- Part-time employed 30 hrs/week
- Took over the development of the new Carswip website from a third-party dev and launched the new site in mid-December
- Also worked with photo editing and retouching, as well as production of web content for the new website

Intern @ Carswip

January 2017 - June 2017

- Primarily worked with UI/UX design and web development, as well as communication-related tasks
- Designed and developed a new web-based product using Ruby on Rails, HTML5, CSS3/Sass, and JavaScript/jQuery
- Conducted market research for a new market, gaining insight into the potential for Carswip on this market
- Conducted a user survey to gain insight into the satisfaction level among customers